<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./EarthBound (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>EarthBound</name>
		<desc>Intergalactic terror stikes the small town of Onett as a blazing extraterrestrial object crashes in the night! The earth now faces imminent destruction by the universal evil threat known as Giygas! Armed with a cracked baseball bat, a cookie and an ATM card, a courageous boy named Ness vows to save the planet from hideous destruction. He must first find his heroic companions, Paula, Jeff and Poo. Will Ness succeed in his attempts to ambush countless frightening monsters as he travels? The ultimate test lies in the impending encounter with the all powerful Giygas!</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/EarthBound (USA)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940827T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ape Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>F-Zero</name>
		<desc>F-Zero is set in the year 2560, when humanity's multiple encounters with alien life forms had resulted in the expansion of Earth's social framework. This led to commercial, technological and cultural interchanges between planets. The multi-billionaires who earned their wealth through intergalactic trade were mainly satisfied with their lifestyles, although most coveted more entertainment in their lives. This resulted in a new entertainment based on the Formula One races to be founded with vehicles that could hover one foot above the track. These Grand Prix races were soon named "F-Zero" after a rise in popularity of the races. The game introduced the first set of F-Zero racers: Captain Falcon, Dr. Stewart, Pico, and Samurai Goroh.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/F-Zero (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Secret of Mana (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Secret of Mana</name>
		<desc>GOOD AND EVIL BATTLE FOR A YOUNG WARRIOR’S HEART.
There is one force in the universe that keeps good and evil in perfect balance. It is called the tree of Mana. But a magic sword has tricked a young warrior into upsetting this balance, spreading evil throughout the land.

Thus, the warrior must undertake a dangerous journey to find the seeds of the Mana tree which have been hidden for centuries. Only then can perfect harmony be restored.

In this incredible adventure, things are not as they seem. Magic swords release evil as well as fight it. Treasure chests hold booby traps. Monsters are friends and friends are enemies. Potions give power, black magic takes it away. Dragons fly, weapons change.

It’s a world turned upside down that you must help the warrior make right. And the only way to succeed is to solve the Secret of Mana.

Brought to you from the makers of the Final Fantasy series.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Secret of Mana (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>3</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadowrun (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Shadowrun</name>
		<desc>Disoriented and confused, you are forced into a race against time, technology and termination. Running in the shadows and cracks between the Megaplexes, survival depends on your wits, your weapons and your wayward companions. Plunge into the dark side of the future, where technology and magic become one, where devolution and destruction are a way of life. Plunge into Shadowrun.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Shadowrun (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Star Fox</name>
		<desc>Lead the Star Fox Team to Victory!

In the distant Lylat star system, imagine yourself at the controls of a futuristic, heavily armed, space fighter - Arwing.

Lead the counter-attack on an invasion force of hundreds of alien tanks, fighter ships, laser gun emplacements and super battleships.  Maneuver at warp speed through fog-enshrouded canyons, dense asteroid belts and waves of the enemy's best defense.  You must use skill and cunning to bring the fight to the enemy's home planet Venom and smash the Core Brain for victory!

* The Super FX micro chip is on-board for fluid game control and special effects previously unavailable in home video games!  The action explodes from all directions in realistic, real-time, three dimensions.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Star Fox (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Super Mario RPG: Legend of the Seven Stars</name>
		<desc>Mario returns in this incredible new role-playing adventure! His latest rival is Smithy, a menacing creature who causes fear and treachery in the Mushroom Kingdom. Mario must recover seven stars and repair the Star Road before he can make his way to Bowser's castle for a final confrontation with Smithy. Powerful weapons, sinister spells and other useful items help Mario to complete his harrowing journey. New friends and old allies support him along the way. Even Bowser lends a hand!</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960513T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Metroid (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).sfc</path>
		<name>Super Metroid</name>
		<desc>Take on a legion of Space Pirates and a new Metroid force as you forge into the covert underworld of Planet Zebes!  It’s up to you and Samus to recapture the long-surviving Metroid hatchling before evil hands unleash its energy.

An army of ominous creatures are poised for battle at every turn of Zebes’ twisted, threatening passageways… including the menacing Ridley and the great lizard Kraid.  Knock down enemies with a killer somersault and swing on an electric beam through narrow passageways!  They’re no match for you and Samus… but wait!  It seems the Mother Brain has returned…</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Metroid (Japan, USA) (En,Ja)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940418T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country</name>
		<desc>Madness and Mayhem in this 3-D Gorilla Thriller!

Donkey Kong is back with a new sidekick, Diddy Kong, in a crazy island adventure! Challenged by the crazed tribe of reptilian Kremlings, they endeavor to get back their stolen banana horde! Armed with lightning-quick moves, chest-pounding muscle and awesome aerial acrobatics, our duo is ready to face their cunning adversaries. With the help of Donkey Kong's quirky family and his wild animal mounts, they squabble and scamper their way through the unending monkey mayhem!</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Donkey Kong Country (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19941121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20181223T223712</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past</name>
		<desc>Venture back to Hyrule and an age of magic and heroes.  The predecessors of Link and Zelda face monsters on the march when a menacing magician takes over the kingdom.  Only you can prevent his evil plot from shattering the land of Hyrule.

In your quest, you’ll venture into twisting mazes, dungeons, palaces and shadowy forests.  Test your mettle with mighty swords and magical weapons.  Or heft a boulder and hurl it at your enemies.  If the going gets tough, dive into a river--you can swing to escape!  Learn powerful spells, locate magical artifacts and solve the mysteries of the evil magician and the hidden realm of Hyrule.

This exciting Super NES sequel to the Legend of Zelda and The Adventure of Link uses 16-bit power to create a quest so colorful and detailed you don’t just play it, you live it!</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920413T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190320T234017</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Castlevania IV (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Super Castlevania IV</name>
		<desc>THE GRAVEST CASTLEVANIA ADVENTURE BREAKS NEW GROUND...AND BURIES YOU IN IT.
A century of Transylvanian tranquility is about to come to a shocking end. Once again the mortifying screams of helpless villagers shake the ground as they huddle against new nightmarish horrors unleashed by the Duke of Darkness, Count Dracula. And this time he has a tombstone with your name on it, Simon Belmont.
You must descend into Castle of the Undead and its gruesome ground, accompanied by the most chilling sound effects to ever tingle your spine. Inside, a freshly dug 11 levels maze features the treacherous Terrace of Terror, the dangerous Rotating Dungeon, the Sunken Ruins of Lost Spirits, torture chambers and creature filled caves. Use your whip like a grappling hook and swing past hundreds of traps and a host of ghost freaks, living corpses and hidden goblins. All while dodging or destroying the unpredictable spitting lizards, carnivorous coffins, and more.
Find the concealed weapons needed to defeat everything from eerie phantoms to haunted furniture. Then prepare to find yourself face-to-thing with hideous torments like the Tongue Lasher, the Darkest Knight, the Bone-Afide Horseman and the Granite Crusher. When your nerves get shot, use your password and take a breather. But forge on, Simon Belmont, because if you though Dracula was down for the count, he's only just begun to fright!</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Castlevania IV (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190321T000534</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Trigger (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Chrono Trigger</name>
		<desc>The 32-Meg quest begins.
The millennium. A portal is opened. The chain of time is broken. A young man is transported into the past, altering the course of history and the outcome of the future. He has to find his way home, but first he must travel to the outer edges of time to repair the world's chronology. On the way he encounters strange friends and foes, utilizes incredible devices and vehicles, and penetrates and neutralizes the fortresses of the past, present, and future. A paradox has been created. If he does not restore the order of time, nothing will ever be the same. He is the one who will become a hero. He is Crono.
*FROM THE CREATORS OF THE ACCLAIMED FINAL FANTASY SERIES
*CHARACTER DESIGNS BY AKIRA TORIYAMA</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Chrono Trigger (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190508T011700</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aero Fighters (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Aero Fighters</name>
		<desc>Aero Fighters (known as Sonic Wings in Japan) is a vertical-scrolling shoot 'em up ("shmup") arcade game released in 1992 by Video System, ported to the Super Famicom in 1993 and the Super Nintendo in 1994.

There are 8 stages in this game. The beginning stages consists of randomly chosen areas from nations of unselected fighters (assuming those fighters have nations). If Rabio or Lepus is chosen, all 4 rival nation stages become playable. After completing all rival nation stages, there are 4 more stages.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Aero Fighters (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Video System</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200825T012108</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter II Turbo (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II Turbo</name>
		<desc>Feel the Need for Speed!

They're back and they're badder than ever! Faster, stronger and with all new moves, twelve of the greatest fighters from across the globe are ready to do battle! Choose your champion and get ready for the big brawl as they try to earn the right to battle M. Bison for the title. And just when you think you've mastered it all, crank it up a notch and go TURBO!

Cover your head as Blanka dives at you from above and hear your neck crack as Zangief hits you with the Turbo Spinning Clothesline. Stare in disbelief as Dhalsim disappears before your eyes and Chun Li unleashes her blazing fireball! Watch in awe as Sagat fights Sagat and Ryu does a Hurricane Kick in mid-air! Survive all this and you may live long enough to become the greatest Street Fighter ever!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Street Fighter II Turbo (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>6</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200825T011001</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Kart (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Super Mario Kart</name>
		<desc>The Super Mario GoKart Park is open for tons of racing fun!  Hit the track with Mario, Luigi, Yoshi and the Princess.  Get tough and lock fenders with Donkey Kong, Jr. and Bowser.  Even Toad and Koopa Troopa will mix it up in an all-out quest for the Gold Cup!  Race head-to-head with a friend or challenge the computer in great, split-screen, Mode 7 graphics.

Feel like a bit less speed and a lot more strategy?  Take a crack at the Battle Mode!  In four different maze-like courses you’ll use Koopa Shells, Banana Peels, Super Stars and other wacky weapons to burst your opponent's target balloons and triumph!

* 2 games in 1 - Mario Grand Prix and Battle Mode
* 8  Familiar Characters
* 20 Different Tracks
* 3 Different Skill Levels
* Battery-backed memory saves your best times!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Mario Kart (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200825T011625</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
