<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Gunstar Heroes.smd</path>
		<name>Gunstar Heroes</name>
		<desc>Gunstar Heroes is a side scrolling shooter. The player has four weapons to choose from, and they can be combined in various pairs to create a total of 14 unique weapons. In addition to the weapons, the player can engage enemies in close quarters combat. It is possible to grab and toss enemies, perform sliding and jumping attacks and a long-range skid.

Unlike most games in the genre, the player has a life total calculated in numbers. Death to a player requires multiple hits but just one death will issue the option to continue from the start of the level or to end the game. Players have unlimited continues.

The main highlight of the game are its boss encounters, which often feature large enemies made up of multiple sprites allowing for fluid movement.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Gunstar Heroes-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tresure</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./M.U.S.H.A..smd</path>
		<name>Musha</name>
		<desc>A spin-off from the Aleste series by Compile, Musha Aleste takes the same top-down shooter mechanics of its predecessors but stages the action in a bizarre universe that merges traditional Japanese lore with sci-fi mecha action.
Instead of commanding a ship, you will actually step into the cockpit of a ninja-styled mecha as you fight through the many levels in the game, with several option satellites that can be configured to use different formations.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/M.U.S.H.A.-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19901221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Toaplan</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pitfall - The Mayan Adventure.smd</path>
		<name>Pitfall: The Mayan Adventure</name>
		<desc>Pitfall: The Mayan Adventure is a 1994 video game developed and published by Activision. A sequel to Activision's 1982 Pitfall! for the Atari 2600, the player controls Pitfall Harry, Jr., son of the protagonist of the original game, as he attempts to rescue his father from a Mayan jungle setting.

Activision developed the game in partnership with Redline Games. It was first released for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System, Sega Genesis/Mega Drive and Sega CD in 1994, followed by releases for the Sega 32X, Atari Jaguar, and PC the following year. The PC release was the first commercial release for the recently debuted Windows 95 operating system. Publisher Majesco Entertainment ported the game for the Game Boy Advance in 2001; a downloadable version appeared on the Nintendo Wii's Virtual Console in 2009.

An extra feature in all versions is the ability to play the original Pitfall! (the Atari 2600 version) after finding a secret doorway within the game. The Sega CD, 32X and Windows ports contained extra (and expanded) levels and other enhancements over the other versions.

The Windows port was based on the Sega 32X version, and was made using Kinesoft's Exodus game technology, which was later used to make the Windows port of Earthworm Jim: Special Edition.[1] It includes 256-colour art, in-game CD music and effects by SOUNDELUX Media Labs. SoftKey version includes America Online free trial software for Windows 3.1/95, Internet Explorer 3.02, Cyber Patrol demo for Windows 3.1/95.

On April 13, 2009, the Sega Genesis/Mega Drive version of Pitfall: The Mayan Adventure was released on the Virtual Console in North America and later in the PAL regions on May 15, 2009 and in Japan on August 25, 2009. It was later delisted on December 26, 2013 in Japan and at the end of 2013 in North America and the PAL regions.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Pitfall - The Mayan Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950714T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision,Redline Games</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pulseman.smd</path>
		<name>Pulseman</name>
		<desc>In the 21st century, noted scientist and computer engineer Doc Yoshiyama had succeeded in creating the world's most advanced Artificial Intelligence. He called his creation C-Life and managed to make her aware, thinking, and feeling. However, he soon found himself in love with this C-Life girl and wanted to be closer to her, so he digitized and uploaded himself into his computer core, where the two "made love" by combining his DNA and her program core. The end result of their love was the birth of a half-human, half C-Life boy named Pulseman. Pulseman was unique in that he didn't need to remain inside a computer to survive, and had the power to channel electricity through his body, using it both as a weapon and as a means of quick transport through the power of Volteccer.

Unfortunately, living in the computer world for so long twisted Doc Yoshiyama's mind, corrupting his brainwaves and his body. Doc Yoshiyama emerged back into the human world, but twisted and changed into the evil Doc Waruyama. Using a system known as EUREKA, which allows for C-Life beings to manifest in the human world, Doc Waruyama establishes the Galaxy Gang, spreading a new wave of cyber-terrorism across the world, and Pulseman must fight his own father and put an end to his gang for the sake of the free world.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Pulseman-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic and Knuckles.gen</path>
		<name>Sonic &amp; Knuckles</name>
		<desc>The story picks up from the ending of Sonic 3 - Dr. Robotnik's orbital weapon, the Death Egg, has been badly damaged in the climactic battle between himself and Sonic The Hedgehog. As the satellite falls back to the Floating Island, landing in a volcanic crater, Sonic jumps off, landing in a mushroom filled woodland.
Sonic knows there are many Chaos Emeralds hidden on the island, including the powerful Super Emeralds and the Master Emerald, the secret to the island's levitation powers. Worried that Robotnik may try to harness this power to fuel a repaired Death Egg, he sets off to try and destroy the Death Egg once and for all, keeping an eye out for Knuckles the Echidna, still smarting from his Launch Base defeat.
At Hidden Palace, Sonic finds Knuckles there waiting for him. They fight and Sonic seems to emerge victorious when Knuckles flees from the duel after sensing someone is trying to steal the Master Emerald. Knuckles races ahead closely followed by Sonic to find Robotnik trying to steal the Master Emerald: It had been his plan all along to snatch it while Sonic and Knuckles were too busy dealing with each other. Realizing he had been tricked, Knuckles reacts by attacking Robotnik, which fails when Robotnik electrocutes Knuckles. Sonic tries to intervene but Robotnik stills manages to escape. Knuckles now realizes his mistake and that Sonic is in fact on his side. They join forces and teleport to Sky Sanctuary.
At Sky Sanctuary, Knuckles and Sonic watch the Death Egg launching in the background. Knuckles activates a bridge so Sonic can cross over. Sonic defeats a rebuilt Metal Sonic on the way to the Death Egg, and manages to board it before it leaves the atmosphere. Onboard the Death Egg, Sonic defeats Robotnik and destroys the ship once and for all, only for Robotnik to get away with the Master Emerald in one of his giant robots. If Sonic hasn't collected all seven Chaos Emeralds and/or Super Emeralds, the game ends here, and the ending in which the Master Emerald does not return to Angel Island occurs. After the credits, the player sees a scene with Robotnik still in possession of the Master Emerald.
If all the seven Chaos Emeralds and/or Super Emeralds are collected, Sonic transforms into Super Sonic or Hyper Sonic and chases Robotnik into the Doomsday Zone. After failing to lose him in an asteroid belt, Robotnik's machine is destroyed, Sonic and Tails return the Master Emerald, and the Floating Island becomes airborne once again. If the player didn't collect all the Super Emeralds, a scene occurs which shows an Egg Robo emerging from a pile of metal. If all Emeralds are collected, the player sees the Sonic 3 and Knuckles logo featuring Sonic, Tails, and Knuckles.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Sonic and Knuckles-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19941018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog 2.gen</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog 2</name>
		<desc>The gameplay of Sonic the Hedgehog 2 builds upon the basic set-up of the original Sonic the Hedgehog game. The player finishes each level, generally moving from left to right, within a time limit of 10 minutes.  Along the way, rings are collected and Badniks are defeated. Star posts serve as checkpoints, where if the player was to lose a life then he or she would return to one.  When the player has collected at least 50 rings, star posts can be run past for an optional Special Stage.  At the end of the last act of each zone (with the exception of Sky Chase Zone which does not have a boss), Sonic confronts Dr. Robotnik.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Sonic The Hedgehog 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19921120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog 3.md</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog 3</name>
		<desc>In single player mode, the player can choose to play solo, as either Sonic or Tails, or as a team, controlling Sonic, with the AI controlling Tails, which is the default configuration. Another player may take control of Tails at any time by using a controller plugged into port 2. The object of the game is to progress through the levels. In order to completely finish the game, seven Chaos Emeralds must also be collected from the special stages.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Sonic The Hedgehog 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Streets of Rage 2.smd</path>
		<name>Streets of Rage II</name>
		<desc>A year has passed since the events of Streets of Rage. To celebrate the defeat of the mysterious "Mr. X" and his syndicate the previous year, Adam Hunter, Axel Stone, and Blaze Fielding met at their favorite nightspot in the city and spent their time reminiscing about their vigilante crusade against "Mr. X" and his organization. Axel and Blaze had moved out of the city after the adventure from last year. Axel has begun working as a part-time bodyguard and Blaze teaches dance classes. Adam has since rejoined the police force and lives in a small house with his younger brother.
The next morning, Axel received a phone call from Eddie 'Skate' Hunter, Adam's younger brother. Skate had arrived at home from school and was shocked to find his house in ruin and his older brother missing. Attached to the front door was a picture of Adam chained to a wall at the feet of Mr. X. The criminals began to retake the streets once more. Beatings and lootings took place regularly and in broad daylight. Chaos reigned in the city, far worse than before.
Realizing that "Mr. X" and his syndicate has returned for revenge against him, Blaze, and Adam, Axel wastes no time in telling Blaze about the unexpected situation and Blaze herself is determined to help Axel out in defeating "Mr. X" and rescuing Adam. Accompanied by Adam's young brother Skate and Axel's friend, a professional wrestler named Max Thunder, Axel and Blaze set forth on a rescue mission, which will take them from the city all the way to "Mr. X"'s hideout on a desolate island.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Streets of Rage 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vectorman 2.smd</path>
		<name>Vectorman 2</name>
		<desc>Vectorman is a series of run and gun platform games developed by BlueSky Software and published by Sega for the Sega Mega Drive/Genesis. The first game in the series was released on October 24, 1995 in North America[1] and on November 30, 1995 in Europe. The games have since appeared on several game compilations, including the Sega Genesis Collection for the PlayStation 2 and PlayStation Portable, the Sonic Gems Collection for the Nintendo GameCube, and Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection for Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3. Vectorman was added to the Wii Virtual Console on February 27, 2007, in Japan and April 5, 2007, in Europe, and in North America on September 22, 2008.[2] It was also released on the digital distribution service Steam as part of the "SEGA Genesis Classics Pack" and as a standalone title.</desc>
		<image>/home/settop/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Vectorman 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Blue Sky Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>
